futureelectronics.com 2010-06-02

# Privacy Policy - Future Electronics

##### I. General

Future Electronics Inc., together with its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, "FUTURE") is committed to protecting the privacy of your Personal Information (defined below). To that end, FUTURE has developed this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your privacy within this web site (the "Site").

##### II. Privacy Statement

FUTURE depends upon the collection and use of identifiable Personal Information including, but not limited to, any computer-generated identification number (including IP Addresses), and any other information relating to your physical, physiological, mental or economic, cultural or social identity (the "Personal Information") in order to provide the services offered on the Site. FUTURE will only collect and use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and only as is necessary to provide you with the services that you have requested unless you indicate otherwise. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, do not use the Site. (Please note that this Privacy Policy shall not apply to any Personal Information submitted in connection with applications for employment at FUTURE, even if submitted through the Site.)

##### III. Information Collected 

**A. Personal Information**

FUTURE may collect voluntarily submitted Personal Information including your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, facsimile number, credit card information, and demographic information (such as, city, state or province and country, or any other demographic information that you may submit) in order to provide you with the requested services available on the Site. This Personal Information is collected and stored only as necessary to fulfill your request. 

**B. IP Address**

FUTURE may collect an IP address from all users of our Site. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We do not link the IP address with personally identifiable information. 

**C. Applets and Cookies**

FUTURE may use applets and cookies on the Site. Applets are pieces of self-executing computer code that may be downloaded to your computer, and are deleted when you leave the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that website and are used for record-keeping purposes at many websites. Most standard internet browsers are set to automatically accept applets and cookies. However, you can adjust your browser settings to refuse all applets and cookies or to inform you when one is being placed on your hard drive. If you choose to have your browser refuse applets and cookies, it is possible that some areas of the Site will not function properly or will be outdated when you view them. 

**D. Other Information**

Certain non-personal information about visitors to the Site is recorded by the standard operation of our computer servers. For example, FUTURE automatically gathers statistical information about the Site and its visitors, such as browsers, pages viewed, and number of visitors.

##### IV. Use of Information Collected 

**A. Personal Information**

All Personal Information you provide to us is used to provide you with the requested services, such as processing your on-line orders, improving the services offered by FUTURE, and enhancing your on-line experience. In addition, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties, as necessary, in order to service, process or administer your on-line request or order. In addition, your Personal Information may be used in connection with surveys, polls and/or contests conducted by FUTURE on the Site. However, in such instances, this Personal Information will only be used if voluntarily submitted by you and only in accordance with reasonable, identified purposes. For example, if you choose to participate in the surveys, polls and/or contests offered through the Site, FUTURE will ask you to submit Personal Information, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, fax number and demographic information (such as, city, state or province and country, or any other demographic information that you may submit). Unless you affirmatively consent to enter such Personal Information, none will be used. Any Personal Information collected in polls or surveys may be displayed to other Site users in aggregate form to advise users' of the poll or survey results. However, data collected through polls and/or surveys are not tied to Personal Information. Information collected through the contests will be used to administer the contest and notify the contest winners, unless otherwise stated at the time of entry. 

In addition to the foregoing, FUTURE may use Personal Information for internal marketing purposes in connection with FUTURE's services and we may disclose Personal Information to third parties in connection with such purposes. As a result, you may receive communications from such third parties. You will always be given the opportunity to opt out of receiving such communications at the time that your Personal Information is being submitted to us. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you can "opt-out" in accordance with Section VIII below. 

**B. IP Address**

FUTURE uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to Personal Information. We may disclose this information to third parties in connection with our marketing purposes. 

**C. Applets and Cookies**

FUTURE may use applets and cookies on the Site to enhance your experience while using the Site. Applets and cookies are used to store and sometimes track your preferences to provide you with customized and personalized services in order to enhance your use of the Site. FUTURE may provide this information to third parties as necessary to service, process or administer your request or order. Usage of applets and cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information while on the Site. 

**D. Other Information**

Certain non-personal statistical information about visitors to the Site, such as browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, etc., may be used to optimize each particular user's experience on the Site. We also track the domains from which the Site was visited and use that data, together with the other non-personal information, to analyze trends and statistics before we discard it.

##### V. Disclosure of Personal Information 

**A. Sharing with Third Parties**

Except as described in this section, FUTURE will not provide your Personal Information to third parties without your permission. FUTURE does not currently sell, trade or rent Personal Information or your IP address to any third party without your prior consent. Personal Information provided to third parties is limited to only that which is reasonably needed by third parties to carry out their functions in connection with servicing, processing or administering your request or order. 

**B. Restrictions on Third-Party Use**

FUTURE requires that third parties who have access to Personal Information held by us comply with certain safeguards, such as using the Personal Information only for the permitted previously identified purpose, and returning the Personal Information to us or destroying the Personal Information once that purpose is served.

**C. Guidelines for Transfer of Personal Information**

FUTURE will only transfer Personal Information to third parties consistent with the principles of notice and choice set forth in the European Commission's Directive on Data Protection ("EC Directive") and other applicable privacy laws. This means that FUTURE will inform you of the potential for transfer of your Personal Information to third parties and obtain your consent prior to such transfer. Where transfer of the personal information is consistent with the purpose for which the data was originally collected or where consent to the transfer has been obtained, FUTURE will transfer the data to a third party only if FUTURE ascertains that the third party subscribes to Safe Harbour principles, is subject to the EC Directive or enters into a written agreement with FUTURE requiring the third party to provide you with an opportunity to withdraw consent for the use of your Personal Information and to comply with applicable privacy laws. FUTURE will disclose your Personal Information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of FUTURE; and (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of FUTURE's employees, the users of the Site, or the public.

In addition, FUTURE may, as permitted by law, provide Personal Information to (a) consumer reporting agencies to verify your creditworthiness to process your request or (b) third parties in connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, or transfer of all or a portion of FUTURE's business, assets or an operating unit.

##### VI. Security Measures 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, however, rest assured that FUTURE strictly protects the security of your Personal Information and honors your choices for its intended use. FUTURE has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access or use of Personal Information and to maintain data security. In addition, we restrict access to Personal Information to (a) those of our employees who need to know such information in the course of their job responsibilities, (b) affiliates of FUTURE, and (c) selected third-party companies, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

##### VII. Links to Third-Party Web Sites

To the extent hyperlinks are utilized to access external or third-party sites, you should be aware that these linked external or third-party sites are not controlled by FUTURE and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. FUTURE disclaims any and all responsibility and/or liability for the collection, use and/or transfer of information collected by such other third-party sites, any content contained on such other third-party sites, and any link or linking program to such other third-party sites. FUTURE does not endorse the proprietors of, or products or services offered on, such other third-party sites. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this Site, you do so entirely at your own risk. You are responsible for checking the privacy policies of these third-party sites to determine how your Personal Information will be utilized by them. FUTURE also disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, copyrights, patents, domain names or other intellectual property interests of third parties.

##### VIII. Opt-Out

You have choices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information for purposes not directly related to the Site. You may cancel FUTURE's services, "opt-out" of receiving promotional materials from FUTURE and/or third parties, and remove your Personal Information from our database by simply sending an e-mail request to FUTURE.

##### IX. Amendment to Privacy Policy

FUTURE reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. FUTURE will notify you of any change to this Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. You have the obligation to periodically visit the Site to review the changes in the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to be bound by any such changes to the Privacy Policy. Any modifications to the Privacy Policy will continue to comply with applicable privacy laws and thereby provide you with privacy protection.

##### X. User Access to Personal Information

You have the opportunity to access, correct and/or remove existing Personal Information held by FUTURE by contacting FUTURE. See the contact information in Section XIII below. If you request removal of Personal Information, you acknowledge that residual Personal Information may continue to reside in FUTURE's records and archives, but FUTURE will not use that information for any commercial purpose. FUTURE reserves the right to maintain your Personal Information if FUTURE has suspended, limited, or terminated your access to the Site for violating the Site Terms of Use.

##### XI. U.S. Safe Harbor

FUTURE participates in, and has complied with the requirements of, the Safe Harbor relating to the European Community Directive on Data Protection. FUTURE's privacy practices are certified as Safe Harbor compliant by the U.S. Department of Commerce.

##### XII. Use by Children 

**A. FUTURE Policy**

This Site is not geared to children under 13 years of age, and FUTURE does not seek to collect Personal Information about children under 13 years of age through its Site. If we discover that such information has been provided and collected through the Site, we will delete such information. Thus, we typically retain no identifiable information about kids. 

**B. Removal of Child's Personal Information**

Parents may request deletion of Personal Information provided to FUTURE through the Site by sending an e-mail to FUTURE with the following information: (a) parent's name, address (and second address, if the child shares two addresses), telephone number, and e-mail address; and (b) the child's name and/or nickname, and e-mail address. This information will only be used to search our databases and deliver confirmation to you that the child's Personal Information has been deleted. Please note that the deletion of your child's Personal Information from FUTURE's database will prevent FUTURE from notifying you or your child in the event of a recall of a product your child purchased in violation of our policies. Therefore, if your child purchased products through the Site in spite of our efforts to prevent it, we recommend that you simply request the substitution of your name for your child's name in our records, in order to be notified in the event of a recall.

##### XIII. Contact Information 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact FUTURE.
